{
    "subject": "resource/Estey_Organ",
    "predicate": "ontology/subsidiary",
    "object": "resource/Welte-Mignon",
    "human_readable": "The Estey Organ has a subsidiary company named Welte-Mignon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.94527268409729,
            "question": "What is the name of the subsidiary company of The Estey Organ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9361026883125305,
            "question": "Are The Estey Organ and Welte-Mignon known for producing similar products?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.932860791683197,
            "question": "What industry are The Estey Organ and Welte-Mignon involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.848349928855896,
            "question": "What is the relationship between The Estey Organ and Welte-Mignon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8464002013206482,
            "question": "Can you name any other subsidiaries of The Estey Organ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.810558557510376,
            "question": "What type of company is Welte-Mignon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6278278827667236,
            "question": "Does Welte-Mignon have a parent company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5521992444992065,
            "question": "What is the primary business of The Estey Organ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5053643584251404,
            "question": "Does Welte-Mignon produce instruments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5039206743240356,
            "question": "Is The Estey Organ known for producing musical instruments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Estey Organ has a subsidiary company named Welte-Mignon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8002_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Welte-Mignon produce instruments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8002_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary business of The Estey Organ?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8002_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Welte-Mignon have a parent company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8002_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8002_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple. Specifically, the document mentions that \"In 1926 the company used the name, Estey-Welte Corporation. That year, it acquired the Hall Organ Company of West Philadelphia and a new built six-floor building at 695 Fifth Avenue as showrooms and salesrooms. This became the company's home, and the offices of the Welte Mignon Studios and the other subsidiary companies\u2014including the Estey Piano Company, the Welte Mignon Corporation, the Welte Organ Company...\" which implies that Estey-Welte Corporation has a subsidiary company named Welte-Mignon."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information supports that the Estey Organ Company had subsidiaries, including the Welte Mignon Corporation and others. Specifically, it mentions in the document that in 1926, Estey-Welte formed The Welte-Mignon Studios of Florida, Inc., which indicates a relationship between Estey and Welte-Mignon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}